

PROFILE

A flexible professional, selflearner, and highly motivated. With 3+ years of experience in software development, focused in front-end stack, certified by Microsoft, but with good skills in back-end and DevOps. I have also skills strong design and user experience acquired bachelor's in а graduation Architecture. in Worked with large projects in insurance and banking projects multinational а bank, always seeking to implement good practices in my work. This performance made me stand out, having become part bank's governance team, which guaranteed me a promotion with just under 2 years in the company.

PRIMARY SKILLS

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript

Angular

Java/Spring

DevOps

Azure

Git

GUILHERME CHAVES SOFTWARE ENGINEER / FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT INFO:

+ 55 11 931 502 706

GUILHERME_CHAVES@YMAIL.COM

LINKEDIN AND GIT:

LINKEDIN.COM/IN/GUILHERMECHAVES GITHUB.COM/GUICHAVESREAL

EXPERIENCE

Responsible for technical decisions on API modeling. Programming microservices in Springboot Responsible for restructuring microservices using RESTful modeling.

Responsible for solving integration problems between

front-end and back-end

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

AVANADE

III 11/2019 - NOW

Responsible for developing applications using BPM platforms, and also using Angular, Ionic and other front-end frameworks.

ASSOCIATE SOFTWARE ENGINEER

 SÃO PAULO - BRAZIL 02/2018 - 11/2019

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARCHITECTURE AND URBANISM

ANHANGUERA UNIVERSITY OF SÃO PAULO

SÃO BERNARDO DO CAMPO - BRAZIL **2/2011-11/2015**

NETWORK TECHNICIAN

EDUCATIONAL CENTER OF PEDREIRA

SÃO PAULO - BRAZIL **2/2005 -11/2006**

CERTIFICATIONS

MICROSOFT

70-480 - PROGRAMMING IN HTML5 WITH JAVASCRIPT AND CSS3

CREDENTIAL NUMBER: BC018BE7-1E66-4C09-B2CE-A61F8764BECF ISSUE DATE: 07/2019

SCRUMSTUDY

SCRUM FUNDAMENTALS CERTIFIED

CREDENTIAL NUMBER: 777046 ISSUE DATE: 04/2020

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

PROFICIENCY LEVEL: ADVANCED

PORTUGUESE

PROFICIENCY LEVEL: NATIVE